Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Last summer. i worked there
and i got pink rot all over my arms...
and i've been scratching ever since.
No way uncle joe is going to
talk me into cutting celery again.
I'd rather work at the car wash.
If one has committed
the unpardonable sin...
i still say he must realize that he has.
Just the opposite. willem.
That is the error of the pelagians.
Now the unpardonable sin
is the rejection of the holy spirit.
Well you can talk theology. john.
but i go back to the bible.
Just look at hebrews 10:28 and 10:29...
or romans 3:23 to 25.
I'm sick of watching this television stuff.
- Oh. joe.
- Come on.
What are you doing?
You know who makes it?
All the kids who couldn't get along here.
They go to california and make television.
I didn't like them when they were here
and i don't like them out there.
Television. If you don't buy one yourself.
the kids go someplace else and watch.
Give the kids a break. It's christmas.
He hasn't changed in years.
And he never will.
Aunt ruth?
Can we use timmy for the nativity play?
We need him to play baby jesus.
Timmy is only six months old.
Stand still.
What are you doing?
Your dad and i aren't too sure...
that you and kristen
should go on the convention tomorrow.
No crib for a bed
the little lord jesus
lay down his sweet head
the stars in the sky
looked down where he lay
the little lord jesus
asleep in the hay
the cattle are lowing
the poor baby wakes
but i was a good turkey this year.
Please. don't eat me.
Don't eat me.
Uncle casey and aunt sue are here.
Let's eat.
Now we'll say grace.
Heavenly father...
we thank thee for bringing
this family together here on this occasion.
Thou knowest our every need.
We ask thee
to watch over us in the coming year.
Keep us safe from harm and danger.
if it be thy will.
Bless all our missionaries throughout
the length and breadth of this earth.
Amen.
Harold jay. please don't touch that.
Sister. would you go and see
if kristen has everything packed?
Of course.
You want to go for coffee
after we send the girls off?
No. thanks anyway.
I've got to get right over to the office.
Anne wants to make sure
you come by for dinner sunday.
Now with kristen gone. you'll be all alone.
You ready?
Don't forget your gloves.
Bye.
See you.
I wish i was going to disneyland.
Daverman.
Debeer.
Deboer. Dejong.
- Have a nice time.
- Devries.
Get a shot of her. will you?
Wave.
Come on. marsha. get going there.
Devries.
Vanderkeen.
Vanderlon.
Vandorn.
- Take care of yourself. kristen. I love you.
- I love you. too.
If you need anything. just call.
Van dyke.
There they go.
They're safely away.
A new shipment came in? Good.
This look all right to you?
- Those the right specs?
- I think so.
- It's fine.
- Okay.
Thank you.
- This all the display space you could get?
- I tried to get more. but this is the limit.
The devries line has the same area.
- What do you think of that shade of blue?
- I like it. mr. Vandorn.
Don't think it's a little bright?
Not really.
but if you want me to tone it down...
no.
I wouldn't hire a display designer
if i didn't trust her taste.
Maybe we could bring more of that shade in.
Perhaps a panel.
No. that would be much too overpowering.
Overpowering. That's the word
i was looking for.
I've worked on this color scheme for weeks.
I think it's just right.
- What do you call that shade?
- Pavonine.
It's the same shade as the fabric.
You still going with that fellow
that teaches over at grand valley?
- Sam?
- Yeah.
Nice guy. You don't want to lose him.
Maybe we could take it down a little bit.
It's just a little...
- overpowering?
- Yeah.
Okay. mr. Vandorn. i think
we could knock that pavonine blue a bit.
- Are you sure it's all right?
- Yes. I think it'll look better.
If you say so.
This is so boring.
I can't wait until tomorrow.
Are you going to
knott's berry farm with him?
He asked me. Are you going with anybody?
I don't know.
- Do you know how to play chicken?
- What's that?
You don't know how to play?
Well. you see. a boy goes like this.
What does it do?
Each time he comes in closer...
and closer...
and closer. until you say chicken.
And then he stops.
Does jerry do that?
Everybody. time for your discussion group.
Marsha. put your nametag back on.
Come on.
Question: What is your only comfort
in life and death?
Answer:
That i. body and soul.
both in life and death...
am not my own...
but belong unto
my faithful savior. jesus christ.
Soon as the church service begins...
the ushers all go over
to big boy's for coffee.
I'll get it.
So when someone like old mrs. Van dyke
in a wheelchair needs help...
there's no one there to help her.
She's right. You never find those guys
when you need them.
Aren't you glad
you came for sunday dinner now?
- It's for you. jake.
- Thank you.
I hope i never get old
and have to be in a wheelchair...
and have to depend on the ushers
to help me out of church.
You'd never let that happen to your mother.
would you. harold jay?
When?
Yes. all right. Thank you.
What is it. jake?
That was mrs. Steensma
calling from california.
Kristen's disappeared.
- What happened?
- They don't know.
They were on some sort of recreation deal
at knott's berry farm.
When they came back to the bus.
kristen was gone and they couldn't find her.
- They called the police?
- Yeah.
- Is marsha there?
- Yeah. she's all right. She's upset.
I've got to fly out there today.
They want me to bring some pictures.
I'll go with you.
I'll check the airline schedules.
Just let me pack some things.
There's a ride called
the great white knuckler. a roller coaster.
The last time i saw kristen.
she was standing there.
Why was she alone?
Was she alone?
I told the policeman.
They had met an older boy earlier.
Mr. Vandorn. turns out
that the boy your daughter was talking to...
didn't work at the park.
We've interviewed everybody there
and nobody there had ever seen him before.
But if she has...
at the present.
there's no indication of any violence.
Let's hope she's just a runaway.
There's something very wrong here.
Kristen isn't the type of person
to just up and leave.
I said. let's hope she's a runaway.
If she's a runaway.
then at least she knows where she is.
That's better than a lot of these kids.
Some of them won't show up for years
and some won't show up at all.
These are the realities.
What are you doing?
I've got two officers assigned to the case.
They're going to follow up every lead.
We're going to give it our best shot.
What can we do?
There are people
who specialize in this kind of thing.
I suppose you could hire yourselves
the best private detective in town.
He might be able
to put all his energies into finding kristen.
Mr. Mast. i'm jake vandorn.
This is my brother-in-law. wes.
- Coffee?
- Black.
Let me ask you a personal question.
Was your daughter
the kind of girl to run around?
Play practical jokes. maybe?
No. i didn't think she was.
Let me get the picture here. let me guess.
Let me visualize your daughter.
She's an absolutely clean girl.
a model daughter.
She never had
a rebellious or impure thought.
She didn't fuck around.
If i were you.
i'd watch my language. mr. Mast.
I'm a private detective. vandorn.
You want to hire a choir boy.
you can go back to grand rapids.
I've been to that scumbag town.
It's full of them.
- Who's paying you?
- You are.
That's right.
Look. i'm sorry. I didn't mean
to offend your personal beliefs.
Believe me.
i'm a practitioner of mind science myself.
Look. i'm good at this. I do it a lot.
Don't worry. i'll find her. No problem.
It may take a week or two.
maybe a month. at most.
Now i get $750 a week. minimum.
It may seem like a lot to you. but it ain't.
You could hire cheaper.
- And better?
- I suppose.
But i got an instinct.
If your daughter's here. i'll track her down.
There's not much you can do here.
Maybe it'd be better if you go back home.
You could look through
kristen's personal stuff. Ask around.
Maybe find out
if she knew somebody out here.
A friend or a relative.
Maybe somebody she knew
knew somebody out here.
Where's marsha?
- How about some cake and coffee?
- Just coffee.
Hello. uncle jake.
Sorry i didn't make it yesterday.
But here's your present. a day late.
I hope you like it.
- Thank you.
- Happy birthday.
Thanks.
- What is it?
- You'll see.
- I'll just go out on the porch.
- Okay. jake.
What is it. honey?
Hello. jake.
- Sit here.
- No. thanks. I'll sit over there.
Spring's going to be early.
A cold spring means a hot summer.
It's going to be a good year.
How's your business. jake?
Not too bad.
You know. you should
come around more often.
We haven't seen you for weeks.
Anne complains
she doesn't see you at all anymore.
You can't dwell on kristen all the time.
Sometimes it's hard for us
to understand the lord's ways.
He's testing you.
You have to have faith.
Would you?
Could you?
- Hello.
- Mr. Vandorn.
- Mast?
- Yeah.
Where are you?
The connection sounds very good.
- I'm back in grand rapids.
- G.r.? Why?
Can you meet me in about an hour?
At the pantlind hotel.
- I have a meeting.
- What are you paying me for?
I'll be there.
Have you ever seen
any pornographic movies. jake?
No.
Do you know what a hardcore movie is?
- Yes. it's like a stag film. huh?
- Yeah.
- Have you ever seen one of those?
- No.
- They're legal now. all over.
- So i gather.
Even here in grand rapids.
There's a little stall theater up here.
It's closed now.
but i got the use of it for an hour.
There's something you ought to see.
It can't be.
Oh. my god.
Turn it off.
Turn it off. please.
- Where is she?
- I don't know.
- Where did you get that film?
- I bought it in a store in l.a. I got to keep it.
- Who made it?
- I don't know.
- What do you mean?
- Wait a minute. Slow down.
A film like this. 8mm film.
it costs $200 or $300 to make.
Sold outright in a store.
Shown in peep machines.
It's impossible to track down.
Nobody makes it. Nobody shows it.
Nobody sees it.
It's like it doesn't even exist.
What's it called?
It was called slave of love when i bought it.
Next time it's sold.
it'll be called something else.
- But the police.
- The police?
You know more than the police do.
You think she's all right?
Yeah. probably.
You like this. don't you?
You liked showing me this.
I hate it. But you got to know. buddy...
there's a lot of strange things
happening in this world.
Things you don't know about
in grand rapids.
Things you don't want to know about.
Doors that shouldn't be opened.
Look. i'll find her.
But i can't make any promises.
I don't know what she'll be like
when i find her.
And when i find her.
you may not even want her back.
Actors. to your positions. please.
Come on. niki. put your wig back on.
Let's get it on.
Yeah. get it together. kids.
Can't you get this bed any warmer?
My ass is freezing.
He's got it up.
- It's about time. The kid's got a big schlong.
- A great talent.
Action! Move it. let's go.
The wallpaper. it's peeling.
- Never mind. Keep shooting.
- We're rolling.
Come on. Keep it up. keep it going.
All right. Niki. throw your legs
around his shoulders.
Bennie. swing around this way
and lick her belly.
Maybe we should use a strobe light.
So it looks like
they're doing more than they are.
For what we're paying them.
they'll do whatever we want.
Quick. get some spunk.
Niki. come on. sweetheart.
Now you're lying back.
You're feeling real good.
You're setting your mind free.
you're thinking about your dad.
Your mind is open. it's just...
- the kid's a good director.
- Ucla.
Bennie. come on now.
Niki. move a little bit more to your right.
That's good.
To your left.
What do you know.
What do you hear. What do you say?
Don't get uppity with me. billy.
I remember when you was running
a car wash.
You couldn't make a go of that. could you?
What was the other thing?
The dairy queen?
That went bust too. didn't it?
Always in action though.
and always made a dollar.
- Right. kurt?
- Right. Always in action.
This girl. she's been doing some porn stuff.
- Do you recognize her?
- No.
Look again. billy boy. this is jailbait.
It could get you in a lot of trouble.
That's no. twice.
All right. I may have to go to the authorities.
You want to listen to me. andy.
You play with yourself?
You must play with yourself.
Will i bother with shit like that?
Look at my girls. They're beautiful.
I'm a father to these girls.
With the money i make.
do i have to bother with that shit?
- You know who's in there now?
- Who?
- Terry. The beauty.
- Right. The fire dancer.
- Very hot.
- Right.
She'll grow hair on your head.
Do you want to hang around?
But you'd better be quiet.
Don't make a sound.
That's really terry?
Move over a little bit.
Back up a little bit
and wrap yourself around him.
Okay. cut!
I'm going out of town for a while.
No. i don't know when i'll be back.
No. there's nothing wrong.
Think you can keep things running?
Don't ask.
- There's a vibe.
- Definitely.
- They have real vibes.
- Yeah. really.
Feels like i could share
a lot of things with you.
- And i try to be giving.
- I like your carpet.
I did it myself. you know.
Shit. it's the cops.
Who the fuck is that?
What are you doing? You son of a bitch!
I've been paying you every week
for four months. You've been out here...
i'm splitting.
I ain't cheated you. pilgrim.
This is research. damn it.
That girl could have told us something.
Research?
I suppose these are the extra expenses
i've been paying you for.
Why the fuck don't you stay
where you belong. back in yo-yo land.
Get out of here.
I'm only human. you know. I'm not perfect.
Get out.
This is my own apartment.
All right. you rat prick.
Go find your own daughter.
I'm not smart enough
to lock my own fucking door.
50 cent admission.
It's a 50-cents admission.
It's applicable to a purchase.
Have you got a film called slave of love?
What we got is just these here.
what you see.
It's a short film.
They're all about the same.
Would you like something?
- This is the movie i'm talking about.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
I just wondered if you'd ever seen this film
of this woman right here.
That girl? No. i never seen her.
I don't know anybody.
Look. i'm trying to find...
- who owns this store?
- I don't know.
Look. if you're looking for somebody.
maybe you ought to check the yellow pages.
- Wait a minute.
- I don't know nothing. man.
You don't want anything for your 50 cents?
Here. take your 50 cents back.
- No. that's all right.
- No. take it.
I don't want your goddamn 50 cents.
Free information. sir.
Want companionship?
Want some friendship? Free information.
Right in here. sir. They'll treat you well.
Hello. Welcome to wild mary's. I'm beatrice.
- Have you been here before?
- No.
What we offer here...
is nude body-to-body contact
on a bed in a private room.
It's $20 a half hour. $30 an hour.
Anything else you may desire may be
discussed in the privacy of your room.
Tipping is allowed.
We accept bankamericard.
mastercharge. american express.
I don't think i want body-to-body contact.
Well. you can discuss that in your
private room with the lady of your choice.
Hi.
I'm looking for a girl.
Have you ever been in a porno film?
Why don't you come back with me?
I'm sure you'll find what you like.
Hello.
- You want a session?
- No. i don't think so.
You sure? We have regular sessions. too.
It's only $20.
Want to see what we got?
See you later. felice.
- You ever been here before?
- No.
What we offer is female wrestling.
Nude body-to-body contact with
the girl of your choice in a private room.
$20 a half hour. $30 an hour.
Any other arrangements can be discussed
in the privacy of your room.
Tips are permitted.
And we accept bankamericard.
mastercharge. and american express.
Yeah.
Do you want to take a session?
I really just wanted to ask some questions.
Yeah. you can do that
in the privacy of your room.
Okay. i'll take a half hour.
- Any particular choice of girl?
- You'll do fine.
Just follow me.
Why don't you just wait in here?
I got to get a sheet.
- Still dressed?
- Yeah. i want to...
why don't you just relax?
Make yourself comfortable. Have a seat.
My name's felice.
There's this girl
that i wanted to ask you about.
Are you a vice? Do you work for
the los angeles police department...
or do you have any affiliation
with law enforcement agencies?
No. i don't.
I have to ask you that.
If you were vice. you couldn't deny it.
You know. you shouldn't dress so straight.
You wouldn't get hassled so much.
Here. let me help you get this tie off.
Actually. i want to talk to you
about this girl. I have her picture right here.
- Pull out your cock.
- What?
Cops aren't allowed to do that. either.
A judge ruled that that was entrapment.
No. i'm not a cop.
As a matter of fact. right now...
i have less respect for the police
than you do.
I'm trying to find this girl. She's a runaway.
I can't seem to get anybody to help me.
- Are you going to stiff me?
- What do you mean?
Look...
that $20 you just paid to get in here?
I don't get any of that.
That goes to the guys that own this place.
I get $2 an hour.
plus 10% of that goes to a bail fund.
I make all my money on tips.
- You want a tip?
- Sure i want a tip. What do you want?
Tips can be what?
Anywhere from. like. $30 to $70.
- What do you mean?
- What do you want to tip me for?
Got to spell it out. man.
Just tell me what you want. Just relax.
Here. i'll give you a tip.
Here's $40.
Now. what do you want?
- I want to talk to you.
- Yeah. that's cool.
About this woman. I'm looking for her.
I want to know if you know her!
Man. i told you. i don't know nobody.
I never seen her before.
I'm getting angry.
Wait a minute. man.
That will cost you more than $40.
- I'm going to find some answers.
- Man. just wait a minute.
Who runs this place?
Is it that blonde guy out there?
Is that who it is?
I'm going to talk to somebody.
Where's the bastard that runs this shithole?
- What's the problem?
- He's causing trouble.
I want you to help me find this woman!
I've been asking everybody!
Nobody knows anything!
Just cool it. Listen. we don't want
the cops in here. You got a family?
I suppose you haven't seen her. either!
Her name is kristen!
I suppose you've never seen her. right?
Shut up!
Knock it off!
Are those the numbers on
bang the nun slowly?
- No. these are for proud pussy.
- Right. read.
- They're very good.
- Just read.
Right.
- Houston is $74.000.
- Yeah. go ahead.
Dallas is $160.000.
- Dallas is what?
- $160.000.
That's a nice number.
Better than the leeway brothers.
They only pulled $30.000.
Who the fuck told you
to mention the leeway brothers?
- They made love muscle.
- Here's your love muscle.
They made it with suzie stretchmark
in a delivery room.
Remember this. i make pictures of quality.
I make custard! You understand
what i mean? I use custard.
Little chicks that come off the surfboard.
You can take them and dunk them.
You can pull them in and out.
Quality. that's the answer.
- What'd we do in st. Louis?
- St. Louis. $38.000.
St. Louis can bang this slowly.
Who booked st. Louis?
Hi. i'm jake devries.
I'm here to see mr. Ramada.
Just a moment.
- Where's my accountant?
- He's got a bad stomach.
He's got a bad stomach?
Hello. What is it. georgia?
There's a mr. Devries here to see you.
A mr. Devries. I don't know a...
you know a devries?
- I never heard of him.
- You ask where he's from.
- Detroit. What'd we do in detroit?
- Detroit? Big. $200.000.
Send him in. georgia.
You never can tell. Who the fuck knows?
Detroit. $200.000.
- You never can tell. He may own drive-ins.
- Right.
- You feeling okay?
- I told you never to ask me how i feel.
Didn't i tell you? All you're supposed to do
is say right. Say it.
- Right.
- That's it. That's all you're supposed to say.
Hello. how are you?
I'm bill ramada. and this is kurt.
- Kurt.
- How do you do?
Sit down. detroit. I love detroit.
Had an all-time box office smash there.
little oral annie. Did you see it?
I'm afraid i missed that.
You missed a good one.
The girl will be a big star. right?
- Right. Big star.
- That's my right man.
- What can i do for you. mr. Devries?
- Call me jake.
All right. jake. what can i do for you?
I'm interested in financing
an adult feature film...
and i was told you were the man to see.
You came to the right man.
Continue. Go ahead.
I have $50.000 that i'm prepared to invest
in a suitable project.
Now. of course. i may want to get involved
in the process of making the film.
Like. meet some of the people who make
this kind of film. learn how it's done.
- I'm curious. What business are you in?
- I have my own business.
We make rivets for the auto industry.
We sell to fisher body.
Rivets? That sounds like a good.
solid american business. Right. kurt?
- Right.
- Sit down. will you?
Why does a solid american businessman
like you want to get into pornography?
Well. i'll tell you. bill.
Is it all right if i call you bill?
Yeah. you can call me bill. Go ahead.
I'll be frank with you. bill.
I've made a lot of money. but...
well. even rivets can get a little boring
after a while.
So when my business manager suggested
that i tax-shelter some income...
i thought i'd give this a try.
- What. the rivet hit you in the eye?
- Detroit's a tough town.
It's cool. you don't have to bullshit me.
You're looking to lay some pipe. right?
Get fucked? Humped? Banged?
Not exactly.
You know. $50.000 buys you a lot of pussy.
You can get yourself pussy-whipped
for that kind of money.
What do you want to fuck
with the movie business for?
- It's an investment.
- It's an investment?
Don't get me wrong. A couple of years ago.
i would have jumped at your $50.000.
But listen to this. Kurt. what did we do
on high school honeys last year?
$5.300.000.
That's $5.300.000.
Does that sound like i need a partner?
I don't take partners. Right. kurt?
But i'll give you some advice.
You look like a nice guy.
You want to take some advice from me?
Start small. with the kiddie porn.
Then work yourself up.
And you come around the set.
I'll see if somebody wants your $50.000.
and you can get into business.
- I appreciate that. bill.
- You appreciate it?
Okay. but right now. i got to go.
I'm a hypoglycemic. my sugar runs low
every two hours. So i got to eat something.
Jake. don't forget my door is always open
to artistic people.
I want you to get me a hamburger. lean.
and some dry toast.
"W/m. 35. 175.
"Fastest tongue in west.
"Will demonstrate proficiency
in all dialects...
"to females under 50.
"Looks not imp." l-m-p. that's in caps.
George harper.
P.o. Box 77. alhambra. california.
- That's going to be on next week?
- Yes.
- I need it out by thursday.
- No problem.
I'd like to place an ad in the personals.
- Okay. How many weeks will that be for?
- Just one.
"Film producer."
That should be in caps. bold face.
"Seeks young men. 18 to 25.
for hardcore film.
"Prior film experience a must.
"Call jake at the cinema motel.
"555-5671."
I like it red.
- How far you girls going?
- Far as you want. honey. We're stranded.
Stranded? I guess i'm going first class.
Cut!
Is that okay?
What kind of army has a soldier like that?
- He brought his own uniform.
- Let's move in for the close-up.
Come on.
What the fuck are you doing?
Making a career out of this?
Too much angel dust...
who do you think you are.
antonioni or something?
- Mister...
- devries.
- Right. Devries.
- Kurt.
Are you the star of this picture?
Are you kidding? Three days' work.
I finish tonight.
- The other girl's the star?
- She thinks so.
What do you do?
I'm with ramada.
we're doing some things together.
Next time you talk to him.
tell him to pay his actresses more.
Paint the grass red. paint the road red...
for what you pay. i don't paint. i just...
don't talk that way to me.
you cockeyed bastard.
Niki. we're ready! Put your wig back on
and take your position.
Nice meeting you.
All right. Come on. get back into the car.
Let's go.
All right. Come on. Action!
How far are you girls going?
Next time maybe we'll get to be the soldier.
you know that?
Boy. us military get special treatment.
This is where we come in for a close-up.
What's happening here. jake?
How did you find me?
I called every la hotel.
Holiday inn gave this as a referral number.
Your office said you didn't have
any business in new york.
So i figured you had come out here.
- Wesley. do me a favor. will you?
- What?
Leave me alone. Go home. Go away.
- Jake. i can't...
- do what i say.
What is going on. jake?
I have an idea of how to find kristen.
I have a plan. but i have to be alone.
What'll i tell the others. then?
We care about you.
Tell them anything you want.
Tell them i'm on vacation.
Tell them i'm on a business trip.
Just don't tell them about this. that's all.
Go home. Go away.
Yes. it's open. come in.
- Jake? Mr. Holcum?
- Pete?
- Yeah. peter long. that's the name i use.
- Right.
We're casting male roles
for an explicit sex action feature.
It pays $100 a day.
Probably up to two weeks' work.
You say you've had experience?
I was in the mitchell brothers film.
sodom and gomorrah.
I don't know if you saw it or not. I played
the slave of the queen of gomorrah.
I got some pictures here...
excuse me a second.
Yeah. This is jake.
We're casting right now.
Have you had hardcore film experience?
All right. supposing i try
to squeeze you in today between...
4:00. 4:15. is that all right?
Yeah. the cinema motel. van nuys. room 7.
Very good. we'll see you then. Bye.
Okay. pete. i have your
answering service number.
- Lf we decide to use you. i'll give you a call.
- Thank you.
I'm dick blaque.
You're doing a porno movie. right?
- Right.
- Then i'm the man for you.
Glad to meet you. but i'm afraid
you're not the type we're looking for.
You mean because i'm black?
- No. you're just not the type.
- What do you mean. not the type?
Man. don't you know who i am?
I'm big dick blaque.
I've done more porno movies
than you ever saw!
I've worked with harry reems. johnny wad.
Not the type?
I can come 10 times a day.
I can keep it hard for two hours at a time.
I'm a woman's dream.
I got a dick hung on me 9 inches long!
I'm sorry. mr. Blaque.
i'm sure you're very good...
but at the moment
i just don't have anything for you.
- Lf something comes up i'll call you.
- Shit!
You don't want to hire any niggers.
that's all.
I knew this was a scam. This is bullshit!
No. i'm very sorry.
but i'm afraid you're not exactly the type.
We have something a little different in mind.
Don't you want to see my stuff. man?
What stuff?
You know. my stuff.
Yeah. sure.
All right. thank you very much.
Yes. come in.
Hey. man. what's happening?
We're casting an explicit sex action feature.
I know. Word's out on the street.
Word's also out
that you ain't really hiring anybody.
- That's not true. mister...
- jim sloan.
Sometimes they call me jism jim.
That's not true. jim. As a matter of fact...
i think you're very close
to the type we've been looking for.
Yeah? Well. i've done
a lot of good work. you know.
Shorts. features. No major roles yet.
it's true. but it's all been really good stuff.
That's what i want to talk to you about.
I've seen some of your stuff.
I like your looks.
I particularly liked you in this film.
I remember that.
It was made by some college kids.
It was called slave of love?
I don't know what it was called.
I never even saw it.
I only got $25 for the whole goddamn thing.
Well. i liked you in it. I also liked the girl.
I really thought she was good.
I was wondering. is she still around?
Still working?
Just wait a minute.
I need the work.
and i want to be in your picture...
but that is one bitch
that i will not work with again!
That was one freaky bitch. man.
I don't know what she was into.
i don't know what she was on.
I just don't want anything to do
with her again. okay?
You know what she did to me? My prick
was so red and sore and chewed out...
i couldn't walk for a goddamn week...
gee.
Cheer up. you're not dead.
Come on. sit up. trash.
we're going to take a little shower together.
Okay. that's it!
- Don't hit me any more. all right?
- Where's the girl? Where is she?
This guy worked her. His name is tod!
- Where does he hang out?
- I don't know. man.
Where?
Look. i know this chick named niki.
She works at les girls. She would know.
She knows where he lives. honest.
- A girl here named niki?
- In one of the booths.
Any one of the first three.
That'll be $5 for two minutes.
It's $5 a token.
I'll take two.
Hello.
Are you niki?
Sure. like in mickey and nicky.
Did you see that picture?
No.
Too bad. I wasn't in it.
Well. it's your money. You talk.
I'm making a film. Jim sloan is in it.
He thought you might know where tod is.
Don't i know you?
Weren't you on the set the other night
with ramada?
Yeah.
- You making a feature?
- Live sound.
You got any parts? I'm free.
I don't really do this.
Jim and i are trying to run down this girl.
Do you know her?
I can't see shit without my glasses. Joanne?
- You know her?
- No. I seen her with tod.
- Do you know where she lives?
- No.
Do you know where she might be found?
Where is she?
- Tod might know.
- Where is he?
The last i heard. he went to san diego.
If we went down there.
do you think you'd be able to find him?
You're not a film producer. are you?
How much you make a week. niki?
You a private detective?
Something like that.
How much do you make?
Here? What a joke.
There was some other detective
asking about that girl.
$300?
This is just temporary.
I once made $900 in outcall.
I'll give you $700 a week. cash.
if you'll help me find this girl.
- Up front?
- Half now. half later.
Make it $900. that was my best week.
Okay. My client pays for it anyway.
- When do we start?
- Tonight. When you get out of here we'll go.
Mr. Mast?
I'm wes dejong.
jake vandorn's brother-in-law.
We met out here a couple of months ago
when he hired you.
Your agency said you might be here.
I'm on a stakeout.
I'm staking out this beer bottle.
I'm worried about jake.
Look. i'm off that case. He fired me.
I want to rehire you.
I also want you to protect my brother-in-law.
He's an angry. unhappy man.
Yeah. unhappy.
You can see that. I'm very sensitive
to people's psychology.
$750 a week. plus travel expenses.
You actually paid for both these rooms?
I thought you were just going to get a
receipt for two. and kickback the deskman.
You going somewhere?
I thought you were going to bed.
I am.
You have any pills? Any valium or librium?
Do you know pimps will sell valium
for 50 cents apiece?
Can you believe that?
I think i'm really fucked up.
I'm a venusian.
The venusian church.
You know. venus. goddess of love.
No.
Take it easy. niki. Calm down.
We'll have a little talk. and then...
you'll go to your room
and we'll both get a good night's sleep.
You got anything to drink?
Want to go out and get something?
I don't drink.
but you can go out if you want to.
- You don't drink?
- Ulcers.
You're not a private detective. either.
are you?
No.
I didn't think so. I've fucked detectives.
Who are you?
- A friend.
- Joanne's?
Yeah. I'm her father.
Jesus.
Her name's kristen.
She disappeared a couple of months ago.
Where's your wife?
She's dead.
Look. don't worry about it.
Your daughter's around.
We'll find her in a couple of days.
You know what your problem is?
You think negatively.
You're a very negative person.
I mean. you got to believe in something.
What do they believe in the... what church?
Dutch reformation.
It's a calvinist denomination.
Do they believe in reincarnation?
I believe in reincarnation.
They believe in the tulip.
What the crap?
It's an acronym.
It comes from the canons of dort.
Every letter stands
for different beliefs like...
are you sure you want to hear this?
Yeah. please go on. I'm a venusian myself.
Well. "t" stands for total depravity.
All men. through original sin.
are totally evil and incapable of good.
"All my works are as filthy rags
in the sight of the lord."
That's what the venusians call
negative moral attitudes.
Well. be that as it may.
"U" stands for unconditional election.
God has chosen a certain number of people
to be saved. the elect.
And he's chosen them
from the beginning of time.
"L" is for limited atonement.
Only a limited number of people
will be atoned. and go to heaven.
"L" is for irresistible grace.
God's grace cannot be resisted or denied.
And "p" is for the
perseverance of the saints.
Once you're in grace. you cannot fall
from the numbers of the elect.
And that's it. the tulip.
Before you can become saved...
- god already knows who you are?
- Yes. he'd have to.
That's predestination.
I mean. if god is omniscient...
if he knows everything.
and he wouldn't be god if he didn't...
then he must have known.
even before the creation of the world...
the names of those who would be saved.
Well. then it's all worked out. It's fixed.
More or less.
And i thought i was fucked up.
I'll admit it's confusing
when you look at it from the outside.
You have to try to look at it from the inside.
But if you look at anything from the inside
it makes sense.
You should hear perverts talk.
A guy once almost had me convinced
to let his german shepherd screw me.
It's not quite the same thing.
- It doesn't make any sense to me.
- Flight to san diego now boarding.
I think it's our plane.
Can i help you with that?
Please pick up
the white courtesy telephone.
Jim rucker runs this place.
He knows where everybody is.
It's a nice place. He hires a lot of girls.
Is rucker here?
He'll be back in a couple of hours.
All right. tell him louise was here.
I'll come back later.
You want anything?
You shouldn't eat all that junk. anyway.
It's no good.
At least i'm a growing person.
Well. you won't keep growing long
at this rate.
Don't start coming down on me.
You know. what i do is important.
There's a lot of guys who can't talk
to their wives or girlfriends...
and they talk to me.
And i make them feel better.
I'm just like a therapist.
You know there's a professor at ucla
writing a book about me.
What do you think i do.
just suck off guys all day?
You think i am just a fuck face?
You can't even say it. can you?
Say what?
Sucking off.
All right. Sucking off.
Now does that make me as good as you?
You don't understand shit.
You don't understand.
When i was 15. i was turning tricks in vegas.
I was taking
all the older girls' regular customers.
It wasn't my fault.
Then they put out a contract on me.
I didn't even know it was illegal.
Look niki. don't go on. please.
You and i. we just have very different ideas
about sex. that's all.
Why? Are you a sex fiend?
- No.
- Well. neither am i.
That's all you do.
It's not all...
look. how important do you think sex is?
Not very.
Well then. we're just alike.
I mean. you think it's so unimportant
that you don't even do it.
I think it's so unimportant
that i don't care who i do it with.
No. we're not alike.
You could never understand
a person like me. I'm a mystery to you.
A middle-class person. A midwesterner.
Goes to church. Believes in god.
And who believes that at the end of his life.
he'll be redeemed.
It doesn't make any sense to you.
I don't know why i should have
to justify myself to you.
I don't care about the things you care about.
I don't care what's happening
in los angeles and new york.
I don't care about the movies or tv.
I don't care who's on johnny carson.
What do you care about?
I care about my daughter.
Hey. rucker.
Remember me? Louise.
Rhymes with squeeze.
You working in san diego now?
No. i'm still up in la. I was looking for tod.
I heard he was around.
Was. He and that shitheel ratan
went down to t.j.
Maybe i shouldn't say that.
Anyway. i hear he's back in frisco now.
- Was he with a girl?
- No.
Okay. thanks.
Keep in touch. baby.
- What's t.j.?
- Tijuana.
- Were they here?
- Tod was.
- He was with ratan.
- What does that mean?
- What does he do?
- He deals in pain.
Is kristen safe?
Let's get a plane to san francisco.
Apparently your friend slipped down
into san diego.
And now he's headed up to san francisco.
How's it feel to have the lapd
doing your police work for you. andrew?
You're going to thank me for this.
You know. the media loves this kind of shit.
Real family drama.
Runaway daughter. enraged father.
They eat it up. It helps their ratings.
Now if this guy goes off half-cocked
and gets himself hurt...
you're going to get such bad publicity.
you won't believe it.
You think this guy's going to
get himself in trouble?
He's a religious type. You figure it.
Tod'll meet you at that bookstore
down there at 4:00 tomorrow.
I told him you were a specialty customer.
Why can't i meet him now?
- Why can't i meet him now?
- He's busy now.
Where does he live?
Listen. i'm risking my ass.
We'll do it my way. okay?
I've been in more motel rooms this
past week than i have in the rest of my life.
At least it seems that way.
Yeah. i know what you mean.
After a while they all look the same.
They are the same.
Do you live in a house. back in wherever?
Grand rapids? Of course.
On your own land?
Just you and your daughter?
Listen. i don't know your daughter...
but...
but. what?
I wouldn't expect too much
about her coming back.
What makes you so sure?
Your wife isn't dead. is she?
Why do you say that?
It's just a guess.
She isn't dead though. is she?
Where is she now?
Back east somewhere. It doesn't matter.
- Does your daughter know?
- Of course.
Your wife left you. right?
Her name was joanne. too.
How'd you know?
Just a guess. What was the problem?
Sex? Always is.
I really don't blame you for saying that. niki.
really i don't.
It's this culture. based on sex.
Sold on sex.
Magazines. music. tv.
Buy this because of sex.
Use that because of sex.
Kids. they think it's normal.
They think they're supposed to talk dirty.
wear scanty clothes.
Hey. don't get upset. I lied. too.
I don't make no $500.
I don't make anything.
Everything i make goes to granville.
- Where?
- Granville.
My old man. Pimp to you.
I split 'cause he didn't treat me for shit.
He thinks he's so cool.
You know. once i tried to take my clothes...
this really isn't any of my business.
I don't want to know about it.
So i guess we're both fucked?
At least you get to go to heaven.
I don't get shit.
Pilgrim.
This is just how you found me once.
What are you doing here?
Look. i felt like such a shit
after what i did to you. pilgrim.
Not that i did anything wrong.
But i kept investigating. poking around.
There's some poor sob in la...
with his face all bent out of shape
where you damaged his movie career.
It's lucky for him no one looks at his face.
- The police want to arrest me?
- No.
They don't care about some faggot hustler.
They're more interested
in your daughter's health. and yours.
- Like i am.
- Yeah. sure.
Look. pilgrim...
you're way out on a limb here.
You don't know what you're into.
- You sure as hell haven't been any help.
- I'm sorry about that.
Now what have you found out?
You got to tell me.
Why don't you tell me something
for a change?
Like what?
Who's ratan?
- Where did you hear that name?
- I just heard. Who is he?
You know. you can buy
anything on this earth.
You can buy child whores. slaves.
Have people raped and killed.
One of the men who supposedly
arranges such things is called ratan.
How did you hear about him?
Just a name.
Don't do anything more.
I'll find out what i can.
- She know anything about this?
- Who. the whore?
No. she's the victim. A dime a dozen.
What's happening?
I hear you've got some money to spend.
I hear you're interested in...
- interesting things.
- Yeah.
Come on.
Do you work for the
san francisco police department...
or do you have any other affiliation
with any law enforcement agency?
- No. man.
- What you got in mind?
I want to meet...
ratan.
What is that? Some kind of chair?
I never heard of no ratan.
Well. i'm told that there are certain things
that only ratan can provide.
Are you talking about real excitement?
Yeah. i heard that you and him
just come back from mexico...
and you got a picture where a girl gets...
- you know.
- Who told you this?
Rucker.
I don't know no ratan.
but i may be able to help you out.
It's not me. you understand.
It's just helping out a friend.
It'll cost you $100 for a single screening.
Is this the one
with the girl named kristen in it?
You got the money?
Take it or leave it.
Okay.
Meet me here today at 8:00. with the money.
- Then we'll go see the film.
- Okay.
Man. you ain't never going to have
no thrill like this.
What's the matter with your room?
- The tv's broke.
- Yeah?
Well. this one's broke. too.
How about the bed. Is that working?
Granville's looking for you. niki.
My name ain't niki.
It's pattica. you know. like in attica.
Real nice.
Granville's looking for you anyway.
- Who's that?
- You know.
The dude with the big white car.
The guy who bought you that ring.
I know that boy. He can make life real tough
on a working girl.
He can get you strung out again.
He'll get you sniffing and then snorting
and shooting.
You both can fuck off.
You're taking a big chance.
I don't plan on seeing him again. anyway.
Oh. no? What are you going to do.
get a job?
Office temporaries? Computer programmer?
Cosmetologist?
- Jake will take care of me.
- Who? Vandorn?
You got to be kidding yourself. honey.
You think once he finds his daughter
he's going to think about you?
No way. kid.
You'll be strictly yesterday's papers.
- What did you find out?
- Just leave me alone.
Look. i'm here to help you.
All right.
Did you find out where she is?
Tod disappeared. I've got to find him.
Where does he live?
What happened?
- Where is he?
- I can't tell you that.
Listen to me. young lady.
My daughter's been missing for five months.
I've gone through a lot
to try to find out what's happened to her.
Now today. i saw ratan kill a girl.
Now i am not going to let this tod
slip through my hands. Now where is he?
But then you'll forget about me.
It's some bondage house. A black storefront
off kearney and broadway.
He works there.
I won't forget you.
What are you doing. pilgrim?
Look. where are you going?
Look. let me take care of this.
I don't want you to get hurt!
Look. don't do anything
until the police get there.
Look. you got to tell me where he's gone.
Hello. police? My name is mast.
Get me joe klein in vice.
Hello. come on in.
Have a seat.
- Now. you need some information?
- Yeah.
Well. we offer...
listen. what are you interested in?
We offer verbal humiliation. bondage...
i'm looking for tod. Is he in?
- I don't know anyone named tod.
- What girls do you have here?
Well. i'm hope. This is faith. charity.
All you have is three girls?
I think you've made a mistake.
Check down the street. Different address.
- I know he's here.
- Wait a minute.
What do you want?
You didn't like the movie?
Listen. i got another one.
I want my daughter.
Her name is kristen. or joanne.
- She was with you!
- I don't know what you're talking about.
The police know about ratan.
They know he's here with you.
They know everything!
Oh. yeah?
Well. goody for them.
Get the fuck out of here!
- Where's ratan? Where is he?
- Let go...
- where is he?
- Who the fuck knows?
The el matador. He goes there.
Don't move. ratan!
Freeze. asshole!
Kristen.
Don't hurt me.
I know it's been terrible for you.
but it's over now. honey.
You can come home now.
It doesn't matter what they made you do.
They didn't make me do anything.
I wanted to leave.
That's not true.
Baby. you didn't want to leave.
They took you away.
I love you.
Don't touch me. you cocksucker!
You never gave a fuck about me before.
You didn't!
So don't touch me now.
I didn't fit into your goddamned world.
I wasn't pretty or good enough for you.
You never approved of any of my friends.
You drove them all away!
I'm with people who love me now.
You robbed my life.
God. baby...
i do love you.
I just never knew how to show you.
It's very difficult for me.
Nobody ever taught me.
I tried.
It's just my damnable pride.
Just get away.
Please.
You really want me to go?
No.
Then you take me home.
Guys. come on. Let's break it up. okay?
There's nothing there to see. it's all over.
Niki. maybe i've...
maybe there's some way i can...
think. maybe. you could
do something for her? Maybe money...
go home. pilgrim.
There's nothing you can do.
You don't belong here.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm